Ira Eaker Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part II: Scheduling File, 1952-1982 (Box II:66-87)
  - 1967
    - 2-3 June, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 14-15 June, Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, McClellan Air Force Base, Calif.
    - 18-19 July, Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Hill Air Force Base, Utah
    - 20 July, American Society for Industrial Security, Los Angeles, Calif.
    - 14-15 Aug., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 26 Aug., American Legion Convention, Boston, Mass. (Box II:74)
    - 5-6 Sept., Kelly Air Force Base Golden Anniversary, Kelly Air Force Base, Tex., (2 folders)
    - 16 Sept., Air Force Association, Mobile Chapter, Brookley Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 25-26 Sept., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 11 Oct., Portland Rotary Club luncheon, Portland, Oreg.
    - 19 Oct., Military Order of the World Wars Convention, San Diego, Calif.
    - 23 Oct., San Fernando Valley Council, Boy Scouts of America, Granada Hills, Calif.
    - 5-8 Nov., English-Speaking Union annual meeting, Hot Springs, Va.
    - 21 Nov.-17 Dec., Vietnam trip
      - General
      - Operation Eagle Thrust
    - 19 Dec., Aviation Hall of Fame, Dayton, Ohio
  - 1968
    - 23-24 Jan., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Robins Air Force Base, Ga.
    - 25 Jan., Cosmopolitan Club luncheon, Washington, D.C.
    - 19 Feb., Copley newspapers conference, Borrego Springs, Calif., (2 folders)
    - 8 Mar., Air Force Association, Tucson chapter, Tucson, Ariz.
    - 12-13 Mar., Air Force Association, Florida West Coast Chapter, Tampa, Fla.
    - 24 Apr., Air Force Senior Statesmen briefing, Washington, D.C., (2 folders)
    - 3-5 May, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo., (2 folders)
    - 16 May, Air National Guard dinner, Sacramento, Calif. (Box II:75)
    - 29 May, Wings Club dinner, New York, N.Y.
    - 1-5 June, San Antonio trip, San Antonio, Tex.
    - 4 June, Air Force Academy Foundation meeting, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 27-29 June, Checkertail clan annual reunion, Pocono Manor, Pa.
    - 23-24 July, Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, San Antonio Air Materiel Area (SAAMA), Kelly Air Force Base, Tex.
    - 10 Aug., Women's National Aeronautical Association dinner, Oklahoma City, Okla.
    - 26-28 Sept., Society of Experimental Test Pilots convention, Los Angeles, Calif.
    - 24-25 Oct., National Council of the English-Speaking Union, annual meeting, New York, N.Y.
    - 21-22 Nov., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Tinker Air Force Base, Okla.
    - 10 Dec., Air Force Association, Colin P. Kelley Chapter, Griffis Air Force Base, N.Y.
    - 16 Dec., Plans and Operations Division, Air Staff dining-in, Andrews Air Force Base, Washington, D.C.
  - 1969
    - 31 Jan., 341st Strategic Missile Wing dining-in, Malstrom Air Force Base, Mont.
    - 1 Feb., Americanism meeting, Grand Lodge of Ancient Free and Accepted Masons of Montana, Great Falls, Mont.
    - 14 Feb., All Officers' luncheon, Naval Air Station, Quonset Point, R.I.
    - 18 Feb., American Legion awards dinner, Indianapolis, Ind.
    - 24-25 Feb., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Ramey Air Force Base, Puerto Rico, (2 folders)
    - 15 Apr., Air Force Senior Statesmen briefing, Washington, D.C.
    - 3 May, Thomas D. White Award, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 16 May, Oklahoma City Chamber of Commerce Armed Forces Week Forum, Oklahoma City, Okla.
    - 26-27 May, Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Ogden Air Force Base, Utah
    - 13 Aug., Apollo 11 Astronaut dinner, Los Angeles, Calif.
    - 25-26 Aug., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, McClellan Air Force Base, Calif., (3 folders)
    - 4 Oct., National Intercollegiate Flying Association Air Meet, Durant, Okla.
    - 20-21 Nov., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Robins Air Force Base, Ga. (Box II:76)
    - 5 Dec., Wright Brothers Memorial Banquet, Beverley Hills, Calif.
    - 17 Dec., Wright Brothers Memorial Ceremonies, Kitty Hawk, N.C
  - 1970
    - 2 Feb., English Speaking Union luncheon, Washington, D.C.
    - 25-26 Feb., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC), Ramey Air Force Base, Puerto Rico
    - 4 Apr., American Fighter Pilots Association, Dayton Chapter, Dayton, Ohio
    - 30 Apr., Air Force Senior Statesmen briefing, Washington, D.C.
    - 1 May, Falcon Foundation meeting, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 8 May, Daedalian annual convention, Kelly Air Force Base, Tex.
    - 27-28 May, Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Newark Air Force Station, Ohio, (2 folders)
    - 3 June, Blanchard Memorial dedication, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 5 June, Air Force Command and Staff College, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 25 July, The National Society of the Sons of the American Revolution, conference dinner, Washington, D.C.
    - 12-13 Aug., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 11 Sept., eulogy to Benjamin D. Foulois, Falcon Foundation meeting, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 28 Sept., Beverly Hills Rotary Club, Beverly Hills, Calif.
    - 2 Nov., Los Angeles Chamber of Commerce, National Security briefing, Los Angeles, Calif.
    - 17-18 Nov., Strategic Air Command, American Ordnance Association briefing, Orlando, Fla., (2 folders)
    - 18-19 Nov., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Kelly Air Force Base, Tex.
    - 17 Dec., Aviation Hall of Fame Enshrinement Ceremonies for Eaker, Dayton, Ohio
  - 1971 (Box II:77)
    - 18 Feb., National Strategy Seminar, Dallas, Tex.
    - 28 Mar., Temple Israel Men's Club brunch lecture, Dayton, Ohio
    - 16 Apr., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala., (2 folders)
    - 20 Apr., Air Force Senior Statesmen briefing, Washington, D.C.
    - 21-22 Apr., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 30 Apr.-1 May, Falcon Foundation meeting, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 6 May, American Ordnance Association Annual meeting, Washington, D.C.
    - 14 May, Southeastern State College commencement exercises, Durant, Okla.
    - 21 May, Department of Defense Seminar for leaders of nongovernmental national organizations, Washington, D.C., (2 folders)
    - 14-18 June, Global Strategy discussions, Naval War College, Newport, R.I.
    - 26-27 Aug., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Hill Air Force Base, Utah
    - 8 Sept., World Affairs Council, San Diego, Calif.
    - 16-18 Sept., Society of Experimental Test Pilots, Los Angeles, Calif.
    - 6 Oct., National Defense Committee, Daughters of the American Revolution, Washington, D.C.
    - 13 Oct., Inter-American Defense College, Fort McNair, Washington, D.C.
    - 18 Oct., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 21 Nov., airport dedication, Morgantown, W.Va.
    - 1 Dec., Lunchbox Forum Seminar, National Air and Space Museum, Washington, D.C.
    - 15-17 Dec., Strategic Air Command (SAC) combat competition, McCoy Air Force Base, Fla.
  - 1972
    - 14-15 Jan., National defense seminars, Portland, Oreg.
    - 14 Feb., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 17-18 Feb., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Patrick Air Force Base, Fla., (2 folders) (Box II:78)
    - 29 Feb., public affairs luncheon, Union League, New York, N.Y.
    - 14 Mar., Oklahoma state convention, Daughters of the American Revolution, Tulsa, Okla.
    - 22-27 Mar., Headquarters, United States Air Force Southern Command, Albrook Air Force Base, Canal Zone (Panama)
    - 10 Apr., United States Army War College, Carlisle Barracks, Pa.
    - 12-13 Apr., Strategic Air Command, missile combat competition, Vandenberg Air Force Base, Calif.
    - 15 Apr., Gill Roldo Wilson Memorial dedication, Daytona Beach, Fla.
    - 20 Apr., National Security Seminar, Fort Riley, Kans., (2 folders)
    - 5 May, Donald W. Douglas (1892-1981), 80th birthday, Los Angeles, Calif.
    - 20 May, The Order of Lafayette Freedom Award, Washington, D.C.
    - 23 May, Air Force Senior Statesmen Symposium, Washington, D.C.
    - 24-25 May, Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 5 June, Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 12-16 June, Global Strategy Discussions, Naval War College, Newport, R.I.
    - 16 June-8 July, European trip
    - 22 July, Minnesota Aquatennial celebration, Minneapolis, Minn.
    - 22 July, 384th Bomber Group reunion, San Francisco, Calif.
    - 16-17 Aug., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 29 Aug., visit with Admiral Emmett Tidd, Rosslyn, Va.
    - 7-10 Sept., Air Force Training Command, San Antonio, Tex., (3 folders) (Box II:79)
    - 9 Sept., Concho County Old Timers reunion, Eden, Tex.
    - 15-16 Sept., Falcon Foundation meeting and dinner unveiling Harold George's portrait, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 19-20 Sept., Air Force Academy Foundation leadership conference, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 22 Sept., 94th Troop Carrier Squadron reunion, Newark, N.J.
    - 5-6 Oct., Military History Symposium, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 13 Oct., Air University, Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 14 Nov., Air Force Historical Foundation meeting, Washington, D.C.
    - 28-29 Nov., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Robins Air Force Base, Ga.
  - 1973
    - 15 Feb., Elements of Command Discussion Series, U.S. Army War College, Carlisle, Pa.
    - 16 Feb., Reserve Officers Association dinner, Washington, D.C.
    - 7 Mar., Command dining-in, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 14-16 Mar., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, McClellan Air Force Base, Calif., (2 folders)
    - 9 Apr., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 16 Apr., National Defense Committee luncheon, Daughters of the American Revolution, Washington, D.C.
    - 1 May, Senior Statesmen Symposium, Washington, D.C.
    - 3 May, President's Committee on Hiring the Handicapped, annual meeting, Washington, D.C.
    - 4 May, Falcon Foundation meeting, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 10 May, American Study Forum, Omaha, Nebr.
    - 12 May, 91st Bomber Group reunion, Washington, D.C.
    - 30 May, ceremony honoring Hugh Knerr, Andrews Air Force Base, Washington, D.C.
    - 21 June, Strategic Air Command (SAC) briefing, Offutt Air Force Base, Nebr.
    - 23 June, Daedalian convention, Colorado Springs, Colo. (Box II:80)
    - 27 June, Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC), Hill Air Force Base, Utah
    - 30 July, Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala., (2 folders)
    - 19-22 Sept.
      - Colorado Springs, Colo., trip
      - North American Air Defense Command (NORAD) briefing material, (2 folders)
    - 28 Sept.-4 Oct., 8th Air Force change of command ceremony, Anderson Air Force Base, Guam
    - 5 Oct.
      - Air Force Academy Foundation meeting, Colorado Springs, Colo.
      - King and Queen Land Co. annual meeting, Stevensville, Va.
    - 10-12 Oct., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Kelly Air Force Base, Tex.
    - 18-19 Oct., Idaho speaking trip
    - 31 Oct., Army War College, Carlisle Barracks, Pa.
    - 28 Nov., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 3 Dec., Tactical Air Command (TAC) briefing, Langley Air Force Base, Va.
    - 12 Dec., Ira C. Eaker Squadron, Arnold Air Society, Loyola University, Los Angeles, Calif.
    - 14 Dec., Aviation Hall of Fame enshrinement ceremonies for Howard Hughes, Dayton, Ohio
  - 1974 (Box II:81)
    - 20-21 Jan., Puerto Rico trip
    - 30-31 Jan., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC), Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 25 Mar., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force base, Ala.
    - 30 Mar.-16 Apr., European trip
    - 9 Apr., Senior Statesmen conference, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 20-22 May, Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Oklahoma City, Okla.
    - 27-28 May, Daedalian convention, San Antonio, Tex.
    - 1-6 June, 30th Anniversary of Normandy landings
    - 17 June, Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 29 June, Chief of Naval Operations, change of command ceremonies, Naval Academy, Annapolis, Md.
    - 2 July, Admiral Thomas Hinman Moorer retirement review, Andrews Air Force Base, Washington, D.C.
    - 27 July, 57th Bomb Wing reunion, Hampton, Va.
    - 13 Aug., Air War College, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 28-29 Aug., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 17 Sept., Air Force Association Citation of Honor, Air Force Association national convention, Washington, D.C.
    - 18 Sept., Air Force Historical Association annual meeting, Washington, D.C.
    - 20 Sept., golden jubilee dinner commemorating the first round-the-world flight, Santa Monica, Calif.
    - 23 Sept., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 26-28 Sept., The Society of Experimental Test Pilots, Beverly Hills, Calif.
    - 5 Oct., O. C. Fisher Day, San Angelo, Tex.
    - 10-11 Oct., Military History Symposium, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 26 Oct., B-1 rollout and air force ball, Calif.
    - 2-17 Nov., Honolulu, San Diego, and Los Angeles trip
    - 21 Nov., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 4 Dec., Daedalian dinner dance, Bolling Air Force Base, Washington, D.C.
    - 7 Dec., dinner at British Embassy, "Winston Churchill: In Commemoration," Washington, D.C.
    - 13 Dec., Wright Brothers memorial dinner, Washington, D.C.
    - 14 Dec., Aviation Hall of Fame enshrinement for T. Claude Ryan, Dayton, Ohio
    - 17 Dec., presentation of 8th Air Force commemorative beaker, British Embassy, Washington, D.C.
  - 1975 (Box II:82)
    - 3-4 Feb., Media-Military Dialogue '75 Symposium, Air War College, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 8 Feb., Carabao Wallow, Washington, D.C.
    - 2-3 Mar., Air War College, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 14 Mar., dining-out, Bolling Air Force Base, Washington, D.C.
    - 17 Mar., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 9 May, "Hail and farewell" to piston-powered aircraft, Andrews Air Force Base, Washington, D.C.
    - 14 May, Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 16-17 May, Daedalian convention, San Antonio, Tex.
    - 21 May, American Defense Preparedness Association luncheon, Washington, D.C.
    - 28 May, Senior Statesmen Symposium, Washington, D.C.
    - 9 June, Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 18 June, Los Angeles Breakfast Club, Los Angeles, Calif.
    - 25-27 June, Current Strategy Forum, Naval War College, Newport, R.I.
    - 16 July, National Youth Science Camp luncheon, Washington, D.C.
    - 14 Aug.
      - Military Airlift Command (MAC) briefing, Scott Air Force Base, Ill., (2 folders)
      - Dwight D. Eisenhower Institute for Historical Research reception, Washington, D.C.
    - 4 Sept., General Carl "Tooey" Spaatz Trophy presentation, Langley Air Force Base, Va.
    - 15 Sept., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 25-26 Sept., Los Angeles, Calif., trip
    - 27 Sept., Falcon Foundation meeting, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 11 Oct., Retired Officers Association, Buffalo, N.Y.
    - 15-16 Oct., American Defense Preparedness Association meeting and Edwards Air Force Base visit, Calif.
    - 21-22 Nov., Air University conference, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 30 Nov.-1 Dec., Strategic Air Command briefing, Offutt Air Force Base, Nebr.
    - 8 Dec., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
  - 1976 (Box II:83)
    - 20-21 Jan., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 22-26 Jan., Puerto Rico trip
    - 1 Mar., Army War College, Carlisle Barracks, Pa.
    - 15 Mar., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 16 Mar., national defense luncheon, Daughters of the American Revolution, Washington, D.C.
    - 28-30 Mar., Media-Military Symposium '76, Air War College, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 3-16 Apr., European trip
    - 20 Apr., George C. Marshall corridor of the Pentagon dedication, Washington, D.C.
    - 26 Apr., birthday luncheon with Air Force Chief of Staff, Washington, D.C.
    - 17-18 May, Air University film project, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 26 May, Senior Statesmen Symposium, Washington, D.C.
    - 7 June, Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 23-25 July, Aviation Hall of Fame ceremonies, Dayton, Ohio
    - 27-29 July, Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC), Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 8 Sept., RAF Bomber Command -- 8th Air Force Association ceremony, High Wycombe Air Force Base, England
    - 13 Sept., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 22 Sept., Air Force Historical Foundation meeting, Washington, D.C.
    - 30 Sept.-1 Oct., Military History Symposium, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 1 Oct., Daedalian meeting, Tinker Air Force Base, Okla.
    - 2 Oct., Southeastern Oklahoma State University homecoming, Durant, Okla.
    - 8 Oct., Falcon Foundation meeting, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 17-23 Oct., European trip
    - 6 Dec., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 7 Dec., Rotary Club, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma City, Okla.
  - 1977
    - 10-11 Jan., Air War College, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 17 Jan., meeting with John S. Postay, director of concepts, Air Force headquarters, Washington, D.C.
    - 2 Feb., Air Force Association civic awards banquet, San Diego, Calif.
    - 19 Feb., salute to Howard Hughes, Los Angeles, Calif.
    - 14 Mar., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 21 Mar., Army War College, Carlisle Barracks, Pa.
    - 25-26 Mar., Marshall Foundation conference, Lexington, Va.
    - 2-10 Apr., European trip (Box II:84)
    - 14 Apr., Industrial College of the Armed Forces, Washington, D.C.
    - 22 Apr., Charles A. Lindbergh lecture series, Missouri Historical Society, St. Louis, Mo.
    - 10 May, Senior Statesmen Symposium, Washington, D.C.
    - 12 May, community dining-out, Tinker Air Force Base, Okla.
    - 20 May, Library of Congress, Lindbergh luncheon, Washington, D.C.
    - 6 June, Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 22 June, Strategic Air Command (SAC) visit, Offutt Air Force Base, Nebr.
    - 29-31 July, Texas Air Force Association convention, San Antonio, Tex.
    - 1 Aug., Strategic Air Command (SAC) change of command ceremonies, Offutt Air Force Base, Nebr.
    - 15 Sept., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 17 Sept., Air Force 30th birthday celebration, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 27 Sept., Strategic Air Command (SAC) bombing and navigation competition, Barksdale Air Force Base, La.
    - 2 Oct., King and Queen Rod and Gun Club meeting, Stevensville, Va.
    - 13 Oct., Society of Experimental Test Pilots dinner, Beverly Hills, Calif.
    - 16-22 Oct., European trip
    - 26 Oct., Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, Tufts University, Medford, Mass.
    - 4 Nov., Falcon Foundation meeting, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 16 Nov., Oklahoma Hall of Fame, Oklahoma City, Okla.
    - 17 Nov., Air Force ROTC, University of Oklahoma, Norman, Okla.
    - 9 Dec., Wright Brothers memorial trophy, Washington, D.C.
    - 12 Dec., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala. (Box II:85)
    - 20-21 Dec., Air War College, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
  - 1978
    - 21 Jan., Alfalfa Club dinner, Washington, D.C.
    - 10 Feb., Army and Navy Club President's Dinner, Washington, D.C.
    - 9 Mar., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 13 Mar., Army War College, Carlisle Barracks, Pa.
    - 28 Mar., Industrial College of the Armed Forces, Washington, D.C.
    - 29-31 Mar., North American Air Defense Command (NORAD) and Air Force Academy briefings, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 11-12 Apr., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Tinker Air Force Base, Okla.
    - 29-30 Apr., Barksdale Air Force Base 45th anniversary festivities, Barksdale Air Force Base, La.
    - 18 May, Senior Statesmen Symposium, Washington, D.C.
    - 24-26 May, United States Strategic Institute conference, Winchester, Mass.
    - 26 May, Collier Trophy banquet, Washington, D.C.
    - 1-3 June, Daedalian annual convention, San Antonio, Tex.
    - 5 June, Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 8-18 June, European trip
    - 24 June, American Fighter Aces Association award, New Orleans, La.
    - 7-12 Aug., Military Order of the World Wars convention, San Juan, Puerto Rico
    - 18 Sept., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 20 Sept., Air Force Historical Foundation meeting, Bolling Air Force Base, Washington, D.C.
    - 2 Oct., United States Strategic Institute board, Washington, D.C.
    - 14 Oct., 2nd Schweinfurt Memorial Association reunion, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 18-20 Oct., Military History Symposium, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 21 Oct., 8th Air Force Historical Society convention, Washington, D.C. (Box II:86)
    - 23 Oct., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 21 Nov., Lawrence Sperry ceremony and dinner, Washington, D.C.
    - 5 Dec., Society of Experimental Test Pilots meeting, Bolling Air Force Base, Washington, D.C.
    - 8 Dec., Wright Brothers memorial dinner, Washington, D.C.
    - 11 Dec., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
  - 1979
    - 6 Jan., Questionmark celebration, Boyertown, Pa.
    - 3 Jan.-1 Feb., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Kelly Air Force Base, Tex.
    - 20 Feb., Industrial College of the Armed Forces, Washington, D.C.
    - 26-28 Feb., Air University Airpower Symposium, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 4-15 Mar., Army War College address and Daedalian dinner, Carlisle, Pa.
    - 19 Mar., Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 5-7 Apr., National Congress on Aerospace Education, Atlanta, Ga.
    - 12-13 Apr., Air War College, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 19-20 Apr., Ira C. Eaker Distinguished Lecture on National Defense Policy, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 30 Apr.-1 May, Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 3 May, Senior Statesmen Symposium, Washington, D.C.
    - 13-16 May, Armed Forces Week celebration, San Antonio, Tex.
    - 30 May, Air Force Academy graduation, Colorado Springs, Colo.
    - 6-11 June, European trip
    - 14 June, Squadron Officer School, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala.
    - 11 July, dinner with Arthur Metcalf, Washington, D.C.
    - 21 July, Aviation Hall of Fame enshrinement ceremony, Dayton, Ohio
    - 30-31 Aug., Air Force Logistics Command (AFLC) Commanders' Conference, Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
    - 14-17 Sept., Concho County Centennial, Eden, Tex.
    - 18-19 Sept., Air War College, Maxwell Air Force Base, Ala. (Box II:87)